ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Recruiting for the Southern Textile War: Labor and Business Prepare for Lengthy Battle, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 31)
  Catholic Observer. December 3, 1976
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Plans Pickets at P.U., 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Princeton Packet. October 20, 1976
  - Item 2: Textile Boycott in North Planned to Organize South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 32)
    The Boston Globe. December 1, 1976
  - Item 3: Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Million-Dollar Stevens' Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 33)
  In These Times. November 29 - December 5, 1976
- Priest Recruits Support for Southern Textile War, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 34)
  La Crosse Times Review. December 2, 1976
- J. P. Stevens: A Target for Labor Black Coalition, News clipping (Box 8, Folder 35)
  The Chemical Worker
- Four Articles from various newspapers., 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Boycott Starts, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Greenville News. November 5, 1976
  - Item 2: Princeton Official's House Picketed, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Philedelphia Inquierer. December 6, 1976
  - Item 3: Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 36)
    The Wall Street Journal (Cleveland, OH). November 29, 1976
  - Item 4: Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 36)
    The Wall Street Journal (Chicago, IL). November 29, 1976
- Two Articles from the Kansas City Labor Beacon and the Independent Bulletin, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Support of the National Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Kansas City Labor Beacon. December 3, 1976
  - Item 2: Workers Flood Loop, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Independent Bulletin. November 25, 1976
- Two Articles from the Chicago Daily News and the Trenton Evening Times, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Princeton Students Protest Trustee's Business Role, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Trenton Evening Times. October 22, 1976
  - Item 2: Union Urges Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Chicago Daily News. November 8, 1976
- Stepping Stone? Stevens Union Is Challenged, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 39)
  The Washington Star. November 8, 1976
- Two Articles from The News and Observer and the Boston Globe, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Corporate Advisers Hired: Stevens' Union-Ousters Get Help, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 40)
    The News and Observer. November 7, 1976
  - Item 2: Textile Boycott Aimed at South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 40)
    The Boston Globe. December 2, 1976
- Our Investment Committee has recently become aware of the national boycott of J. P. Stevens products., 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 41)
  Sisters of Loretto. November 9, 1976
- Union Urges Buyer Boycott On Clothing Firm, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 42)
  The Cleveland Press. November 11, 1976
- Boycott J. P. Stevens Textile Products, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 43)
  Daily Cardinal. November 11, 1976
- Don't Buy, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 44)
  New York Teacher. November 7, 1976
- Stevens Hearing Delayed, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 45)
  Greenville Piedmont. November 2, 1976
- Union Urges Boycott of Textile Firm, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 46)
  St. Louis Globe- Democrat. October 30, 1976
- J. P. Stevens In Contempt Of Court For Refusal To Bargain With ACTWU, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 47)
  Galesburg Labor News. October 21, 1976
- Trustee Is Target, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 48)
  Princeton Town Topics. October 21, 1976
- Support Pressed For J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 49)
  Los Angeles Citizen. October 15, 1976
- AFL-CIO To Boycott J. P. Stevens Textiles, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 50)
  The Cleveland Press. September 9, 1976
- NLRB Hearings Turn To Stevens Changes, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 51)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. December 15, 1976
- Textiles Target Of Labor Push Into Southland, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 52)
  The Cincinnati Enquirer. November 7, 1976
- Boycott May Be Unnoticed, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 53)
  Greensboro Daily News. November 7, 1976
- Stevens Employe Group Seeks Hearing To Oust Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 54)
  Durham Herald. October 28, 1976
- Stevens Agrees To Rehire Worker, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 55)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. December 14, 1976
- Stevens Says ACTWU Not Bargaining Unit, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 56)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. December 16, 1976
- The Southern Textile War, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 57)
  The Nation. October 2, 1976
- On The Road Again: The Textile/Apparel Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 58)
  Clothes. September 15, 1976
- Some Stevens Employes Seek to Oust Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 59)
  Daily News Record. October 14, 1976
- Stevens-Union Hearings Underway, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 60)
  This Week. December 16, 1976
- These Are Some J. P. Stevens Products, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 61)
  Free For All. December 15, 1976
- In the past few months, we have been so busy with our effor, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 62)
  J. P. Stevens Employees Educational Committee. December 15, 1976
- Unions to Gear Up Boycott Of Stevens' Products Today, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 63)
  September 6, 1976.
- NLRB Begings Hearings On Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 64)
  Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. December 13 1976
- Union Is Boycotting Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 65)
  Kannapolis Independent. September 6, 1976
- No Kickoff For Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 66)
  Greenville Piedmont. September 8, 1976
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: New Labor Press Series Will Feature J-P Stevens: Union Boycott Support Urged, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 67)
    AFL-CIO Milwaukee Labor Press. December 9, 1976
  - Item 2: NLRB Charges J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Greenville News- Piedmont. December 18 1976
  - Item 3: Textile Boycott Begins, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 67)
    Peninsula Herald. December 18, 1976
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Major boycott against non-union J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Advertising Age. December 13, 1976
  - Item 2: NLRB Hearings Switched To D.C., 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Roanoke Rapids Herald. December 22, 1976
  - Item 3: Pro-Union J. P. Stevens Worker Wins Reinstatement, Back Pay, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 68)
    Indianapolis Leader. December 31, 1976
- J. P. Stevens Company vs. the Union: The Helen Newsome Episode, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 69)
  Carolina This Week. December 19, 1976
- Stevens Under Siege, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 70)
  Greenville News. December 20, 1976
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Abuses Charged: Textile Firm Is Target of Activists, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 71)
    The Atlanta Constitution. December 20, 1976
  - Item 2: Catholic Conference Urges Aid To Union Organizing In South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 71)
    Indianapolis Leader. December 10, 1976
  - Item 3: Stevens Boycott Sought, 1977; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 71)
    St. Paul Pioneer Press. January 15, 1977
- AFL-CIO Team Claims Big 1976 Gains In South, News clipping (Box 8, Folder 72)
  The Charlotte Observer. December 23, 1976
- Seek 'Economic Justice:' Leading Southerners Unite To Aid J. P. Stevens Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 73)
  Press Associates. December 27, 1976
- Southern Stonewall, 1977; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 74)
  The New York Times. August 12, 1977
- Boycott Threat For Textiles, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 75)
  La Grange News. August 13, 1976
- Two articles from The New York Times, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens: Labor's Big Domino, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 76)
    The New York Times. August 15, 1976
  - Item 2: The Boycott Pace-Setter, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Labor Rallies For Boycott of J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 77)
  The Sunday Star- Ledger. December 10, 1978
- Buying Should Produce Shame, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 78)
  San Francisco Examiner. December 17, 1978
- Two Articles from Women's Wear Daily (WWD), 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Round One: The Issues Are Drawn, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 79)
    Women's Wear Daily (WWD). August 4, 1976
  - Item 2: J. P. Stevens Round Two: The Sides Are Forming, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Two Articles from the Daily News Record, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: ACTW v. Mills: Today J. P. Stevens, Tomorrow The South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 80)
    Daily News Record. August 4, 1976
  - Item 2: The Workers: Stuck in the Middle as Usual, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 80)
- ACTW's Stevens Boycott: Stage Set for Long Siege, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 81)
  Daily News Record. August 5, 1976
- Boycotts should Be Banned, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 82)
  Garland News. August 15, 1976
- Wage-Price Rules Assailed As Compounding Inequity, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 83)
  AFL-CIO News. December 2, 1978
- Two Articles from the Daily News Record, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Don't 'Cave In' to Strikes Pay Council Tell Industry, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Item 2: Mounting Trade Deficit Adds to Inflation Woes, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 84)
    AFL- CIO News. December 2, 1978
- Rain, Blockade Fail to Dampen Labor Rally, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 85)
  Home News. December 10, 1978
- Two Articles from The Catholic Sun, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 86)
    The Catholic Sun. December 13, 1978
  - Item 2: Stevens Boycott Support Grows, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 86)
- House Unit: 'Tis Better to Take Arms Against Sea of Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 87)
  Daily News Record. December 14, 1978
- Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 88)
  Catholic Herald. December 14, 1978
- A Textile Workers Union and the J. P. Stevens Company, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 89)
  Burrelle's TV Clips: Susan Spencer. December 15, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Company and the Textile Workers Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 90)
  Burrelle's TV Clips: Robert Foster. December 15, 1978
- Labor's Love Lost, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 91)
  The Washington Star. December 19, 1978
- Union Threatens Right To Work, 1977; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 92)
  Lansing Sun Journal. December 10, 1977
- Business Notes, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 93)
  America's Textiles. April 1976
- Pay Raise at Chatham Possible, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 94)
  Elkin Tribune. April 26, 1976
- Twelve Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: 2 Big Unions Plan Merger For Textile Boycott in Dixie, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Daily News. June 1, 1976
  - Item 2: ACW's Finley Cites Cost-of-Living Raise, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Daily News Record. June 2, 1976
  - Item 3: ACW-TWU Merger: Early Vote Expected On Stevens Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Daily News Record. June 1, 1976
  - Item 4: Blue Collar Views: Union Has Trouble Sewing Up Firm, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Chicago Tribune. May 11, 1976
  - Item 5: Does Freeman Tell All?, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Kannapolis Independent. May 17, 1976
  - Item 6: Merged ACW-TWU Seen Ready to Test Muscles, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Item 7: Stevens Discounts Effect of Any Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Daily News Record. May 25, 1976
  - Item 8: Textile Unions Merge and Plan Drive in South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    The New York Times. June 2, 1976
  - Item 9: Textile Unions Vote To Merge and Plan To Organize South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Item 10: Unemployment Insurance, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    The Wall Street Journal. May 25, 1976
  - Item 11: Stevens Breaks Silence, Explains Antiunion Stand, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Greenville News. June 10, 1976
  - Item 12: Stevens: Employes Don't Want Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 95)
    Gastonia Gazette. June 10, 1976
- Eleven Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: 2 Textile Unions To Merge, Begin Boycott Of Firm, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    St. Louis Post-Dispatch. June 2, 1976
  - Item 2: 2 Textile Unions To Merge, Boycott Southern Company, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    The Washington Post. May 30, 1976
  - Item 3: Boycott of Century Planned Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    Dallas Times Herald. June 1, 1976
  - Item 4: Clothing, Textile Unions Will Merge, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    Albany Times Union. June 2, 1976
  - Item 5: New Union Launches Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    The Detroit Free Press. June 4, 1976
  - Item 6: Stevens Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    The Boston Globe. June 10, 1976
  - Item 7: Textile Firm Charged With Labor Violations, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    Rochester Times-Union. June 1, 1976
  - Item 8: Textile Unions Ready to Form Giant Union, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    Sacramento Union. June 1, 1976
  - Item 9: Two Big Textile Unions Merge; to Fight Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    New Orleans Times-Picayune. June 2, 1976
  - Item 10: Union Merger Spurs Buyer Fabric Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    Plattsburgh Press-Republican. June 1, 1976
  - Item 11: Unions Set Textile Push, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 96)
    The Washington Star. May 30, 1976
- Textile Workers Rap Belgian Contract Win, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 97)
  Saco Journal. May 13, 1976
- Mill Chief: Raise Output, Pay, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 98)
  Daily News Record. May 21, 1976
- Anti-Labor Consultants: Play Games With Labor Press, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 99)
  July 24, 1976.
- "Hundreds of Companies" Just As Bad; So Says J. P. Stevens, News clipping (Box 8, Folder 100)
  Statement of J. P. Stevens and Co.
- J. P. Stevens and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 1)
  National Labor Relations Board Division of Judges. Case numbers 11-CA-6038, 11-CA-6207, 11-CA-6895
- News clippings, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: ACTWU Says Stevens Misrepresented Time Spent In Talks, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Roanoke Rapids Sunday Herald. June 12, 1977
  - Item 2: Assails 'unbridled arrogance': NLRB Judge Upsets Stevens Vote, Says ACTWU Represents Workers, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Press Associates. March 4, 1978
  - Item 3: Church Groups Lend Support To Textile Workers' Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The Washington Post. March 21, 1978
  - Item 4: Comments on interview with James Finley, Stevens' Chief Executive Officer, 1975; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    To TWUA and Stevens Campaign supporters. November 19, 1975
  - Item 5: Draft of letter to Senators and AAs, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Murray Finley, Jacob Sheinkman, Sol Stetin, William DuChessi. May 25, 2978
  - Item 6: Due To Court Ruling: Union Promoters In Stevens Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The Atlanta Journal. May 26, 1978
  - Item 7: Former Union Activist Returning to Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The Greenville News. March 28, 1978
  - Item 8: Hearings Center On Respirator Program, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. April 22, 1977
  - Item 9: How the Union Got the Upper Hand on J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Fortune. June 19, 1978
  - Item 10: In Organizing Drive: Labor Unions in South Encounter Resistance, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: J. P. Stevens Turns Down Invitation to Move Here: Firm Owns Possible Site, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The Greenville Nes. March 28, 1978
  - Item 12: J. P. Stevens: Anatomy of an Outlaw, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Reprint from AFL-CIO American Federationist. April 1976
  - Item 13: J. P. Stevens: The Last of the Robber Barons, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Independent Press. March 23, 1977
  - Item 14: Labor Reform? Not This Bill, Unfortunately, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The Charlotte Observer. May 21, 1978
  - Item 15: Legal: Recent Major Decisions, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Massive fines face textile giant: U.S. Suprem Court Turns Down J. P. Stevens' Contempt Appeal, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Press Associates. February 27, 1978
  - Item 17: S.C. Says 'Y'all Come' To J. P. Stevens, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Observer.
  - Item 18: Senate panel holds brief hearings: Labor Law Reform Supporters Seek Solution to Deadlock, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Press Associates. March 7, 1978
  - Item 19: Shareholders, the Union, and Hollywood, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Textile World. April 1978
  - Item 20: Stevens Assails Union, Responding to Charges, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Stevens Boycotters Plan Action at J. W. Robinson, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Women's Wear Daily (WWD). January 27, 1978
  - Item 22: Stevens Supervisors Testify On Double Shift Policy, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. April 20, 1977
  - Item 23: Textile, apparel workers hit hard: Union-Industry Group Calls For Action To Stem Rising Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: The Cotton Mills Back Home, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Reprint from Mother Jones. April 1977
  - Item 25: Unions Challenge South In Courts, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 2)
    The State. November 18, 1977
- News clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: "The Cotton Mill Crusade" to Examine Attempts to Unionize Textile Company, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    CBS Radio. September 17, 1979
  - Item 2: A New Blow Aimed at J. P. Stevens, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Daily News. September 9
  - Item 3: Act II for ACTWU, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Clothes. March 15, 1978
  - Item 4: ACTW Cancels Charges Against Stevens' Plant, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: ACTW Voted At High Point Stevens Plant, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Daily News Record. October 8, 1979
  - Item 6: An Open Challenge to the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Committee Against the Union
  - Item 7: Both Sides Have Their Say, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Spartanburg Herald. March 8, 1978
  - Item 8: Correction, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The New York Times. July 20, 1978
  - Item 9: Hearing Set for Union-Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Bull Mountain Bugle. January 11, 1978
  - Item 10: In the Land of Cheap Labor: Hooded Anachronisms, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: J. P. Stevens, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: J. P. Stevens' 30 Years' War, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Record. August 9, 1979
  - Item 13: J. P. Stevens Administrator Defends Textile Company Against Union Accusations, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Cornell Daily Sun. April 19, 1978
  - Item 14: J. P. Stevens and Its Workers Consider Contrasting Reports, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Carolina Indian. March 9, 1979
  - Item 15: J. P. Stevens Announces Union Accord, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The News World.
  - Item 16: J. P. Stevens Employes At High Point, N.C., Vote for Unionization, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Wall Street Journal. October 8, 1979
  - Item 17: J. P. Stevens vs. the Union: Stevens Uncaring, Employee Claims; Union Gains Offset By Strikes, Fain Says, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Martinsville Bulletin. January 8, 1978
  - Item 18: Judge Orders Stevens Rehirings, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Greenville News. May 16, 1978
  - Item 19: Labor Pains, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    TRB. May 13, 1978
  - Item 20: Labor Strikes at J. P. Stevens by Invading 'Wall St.' and Demanding Top Bank Shakeup, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Inside Labor May 23, 1978
  - Item 21: New Boycott Leaflets Document Stevens' Abuses, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: New York Governor Draws Rebuke For His Stand Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Anderson Independent. March 30, 1978
  - Item 23: NLRB Recommends ACTWU be Recognized Without Vote at JPS, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Roanoke Rapids Daily Herald. August 24, 1978
  - Item 24: Order J. P. Stevens To Reimburse Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Daily News. August 25, 1979
  - Item 25: Plenty of Good to Report Here, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Greenville News. March 7, 1978
  - Item 26: Put Up or Shut Up: Stevens Makes Election Challenge, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Anderson Daily Mail. April 5, 1978
  - Item 27: Something to Smile About, 1976; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Father John Catoir. The Beacon. January 5, 1978
  - Item 28: State Labor Council Boycotting Textile Manufacturer's Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Nashville Banner. August 26, 1977
  - Item 29: Stevens Charged With Violations, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Enterprise. January 11, 1978
  - Item 30: Stevens Chief Backs Policy, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    New York Daily News. March 8, 1978
  - Item 31: Stevens' Chief Hits Union For 'Pressuring' Banks, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Daily News Record. March 20, 19778
  - Item 32: Stevens Co. Affair, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Hornell Tribune. July 6, 1978
  - Item 33: Stevens Co. Affair, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Welssville Reporter. July 10, 1978
  - Item 34: Stevens Is Told: Pay Union, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Charlotte Observer. August 23, 1979
  - Item 35: Stevens Profits Double, But Workers' Wages Fall Further and Further Behind, News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    ACTWU
  - Item 36: Steven's Side of Story, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Colorado Springs Gazette Telegram. June 26, 1978
  - Item 37: Stevens Stockholders Hear Union Gripes, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    The Charlotte Observer. March 8, 1978
  - Item 38: Stevens Struggle Is Theme As ACTW Meeting Opens, 1978; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Stevens Workers in Roanoke Rapids Hail 5 Years of Gains With ACTWU, 1979; News clipping (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Press Release. August 27, 1979